freeforcommercialuse.net 2019-07-04

# Privacy Policy » FREE for commercial use photos.

### 1\. An overview of data protection

**General**  
The following gives a simple overview of what happens to your personal information when you visit our website. Personal information is any data with which you could be personally identified. Detailed information on the subject of data protection can be found in our privacy policy found below.

 **Data collection on our website**

 **Who is responsible for the data collection on this website?**  
The data collected on this website are processed by the website operator. The operator's contact details can be found in the website's required legal notice.

 **How do we collect your data?**  
Some data are collected when you provide it to us. This could, for example, be data you enter on a contact form. Other data are collected automatically by our IT systems when you visit the website. These data are primarily technical data such as the browser and operating system you are using or when you accessed the page. These data are collected automatically as soon as you enter our website.

 **What do we use your data for?**  
Part of the data is collected to ensure the proper functioning of the website. Other data can be used to analyze how visitors use the site.

 **What rights do you have regarding your data?**  
You always have the right to request information about your stored data, its origin, its recipients, and the purpose of its collection at no charge. You also have the right to request that it be corrected, blocked, or deleted. You can contact us at any time using the address given in the legal notice if you have further questions about the issue of privacy and data protection. You may also, of course, file a complaint with the competent regulatory authorities.

 **Analytics and third-party tools**  
When visiting our website, statistical analyses may be made of your surfing behavior. This happens primarily using cookies and analytics. The analysis of your surfing behavior is usually anonymous, i.e. we will not be able to identify you from this data. You can object to this analysis or prevent it by not using certain tools. Detailed information can be found in the following privacy policy. You can object to this analysis. We will inform you below about how to exercise your options in this regard.

### 2\. General information and mandatory information

**Data protection**  
The operators of this website take the protection of your personal data very seriously. We treat your personal data as confidential and in accordance with the statutory data protection regulations and this privacy policy. If you use this website, various pieces of personal data will be collected. Personal information is any data with which you could be personally identified. This privacy policy explains what information we collect and what we use it for. It also explains how and for what purpose this happens. Please note that data transmitted via the internet (e.g. via email communication) may be subject to security breaches. Complete protection of your data from third-party access is not possible.

 **Notice concerning the party responsible for this website**

The party responsible for processing data on this website is:  
Markus Spiske  
Dorfbrunnenstraße  
91094 Langensendelbach  
Contact: [info@subwaytree.com](mailto:info@subwaytree.com "FFCU Email")

The responsible party is the natural or legal person who alone or jointly with others decides on the purposes and means of processing personal data (names, email addresses, etc.).

 **Revocation of your consent to the processing of your data**  
Many data processing operations are only possible with your express consent. You may revoke your consent at any time with future effect. An informal email making this request is sufficient. The data processed before we receive your request may still be legally processed.

 **Right to data portability**  
You have the right to have data which we process based on your consent or in fulfillment of a contract automatically delivered to yourself or to a third party in a standard, machine-readable format. If you require the direct transfer of data to another responsible party, this will only be done to the extent technically feasible.

 **SSL or TLS encryption**  
This site uses SSL or TLS encryption for security reasons and for the protection of the transmission of confidential content, such as the inquiries you send to us as the site operator. You can recognize an encrypted connection in your browser's address line when it changes from "http://" to "https://" and the lock icon is displayed in your browser's address bar. If SSL or TLS encryption is activated, the data you transfer to us cannot be read by third parties.

 **Information, blocking, deletion**  
As permitted by law, you have the right to be provided at any time with information free of charge about any of your personal data that is stored as well as its origin, the recipient and the purpose for which it has been processed. You also have the right to have this data corrected, blocked or deleted. You can contact us at any time using the address given in our legal notice if you have further questions on the topic of personal data.

 **Opposition to promotional emails**  
We hereby expressly prohibit the use of contact data published in the context of website legal notice requirements with regard to sending promotional and informational materials not expressly requested. The website operator reserves the right to take specific legal action if unsolicited advertising material, such as email spam, is received.

### 3\. Data collection on our website

**Cookies**  
Some of our web pages use cookies. Cookies do not harm your computer and do not contain any viruses. Cookies help make our website more user-friendly, efficient, and secure. Cookies are small text files that are stored on your computer and saved by your browser. Most of the cookies we use are so-called "session cookies." They are automatically deleted after your visit. Other cookies remain in your device's memory until you delete them. These cookies make it possible to recognize your browser when you next visit the site.

You can configure your browser to inform you about the use of cookies so that you can decide on a case-by-case basis whether to accept or reject a cookie. Alternatively, your browser can be configured to automatically accept cookies under certain conditions or to always reject them, or to automatically delete cookies when closing your browser. Disabling cookies may limit the functionality of this website.

Cookies which are necessary to allow electronic communications or to provide certain functions you wish to use (such as the shopping cart) are stored pursuant to Art. 6 paragraph 1, letter f of DSGVO. The website operator has a legitimate interest in the storage of cookies to ensure an optimized service provided free of technical errors. If other cookies (such as those used to analyze your surfing behavior) are also stored, they will be treated separately in this privacy policy.

 **Server log files**  
The website provider automatically collects and stores information that your browser automatically transmits to us in "server log files". These are:  
• Browser type and browser version  
• Operating system used  
• Referrer URL  
• Host name of the accessing computer  
• Time of the server request  
• IP address

These data will not be combined with data from other sources. The basis for data processing is Art. 6 (1) (b) DSGVO, which allows the processing of data to fulfill a contract or for measures preliminary to a contract.

### 4\. Analytics and advertising & affiliates

**WordPress Stats**  
This website uses the WordPress Stats tool to perform statistical analyses of visitor traffic. This service is provided by Automattic Inc., 60 29th Street # 343, San Francisco, CA 94110-4929, USA.

WordPress Stats uses cookies that are stored on your computer and allow an analysis of the use of the website. The information generated by the cookies about the use of our website is stored on servers in the USA. Your IP address will be anonymized after processing and before storage.

WordPress Stats cookies remain on your device until you delete them.

The storage of "WordPress Stats" cookies is based on Art. 6 (1) (f) DSGVO. The website operator has a legitimate interest in analyzing user behavior to optimize both its website and its advertising. You can configure your browser to inform you about the use of cookies so that you can decide on a case-by-case basis whether to accept or reject a cookie. Alternatively, your browser can be configured to automatically accept cookies under certain conditions or to always reject them, or to automatically delete cookies when closing your browser. The functionality of our services may be limited when cookies are disabled.

You can object to the collection and use of your data at any time with future effect by clicking on this link and setting an opt-out cookie in your browser: https://www.quantcast.com/opt-out/. If you delete the cookies on your computer, you will have to set the opt-out cookie again.

**Affiliates Tools – BuySellAds**  
There are embed banner advertising on this website which is supplied by the provider BuySellAds.com Inc. (P.O. Box 55071 #30027, Boston, MA 02205-5071, USA) “BuySellAds”).

Adverts placed via the BuySellAds advertising network can be shown to you in various formats (e.g. text, images, videos). Which adverts you see may depend on your previous usage behavior on other websites that likewise participate in the BuySellAds advertising network.

The following factors can also determine which adverts are placed for you: websites you have visited and apps on your device; anonymous identifiers linked to your mobile devices; previous interactions with adverts or advertising services of BuySellAds.

You can object to the collection of data for these purposes by deactivating cookies in your browser or device setting. Additional information on privacy in connection with BuySellAds.com Inc. can be found here: www.buysellads.com/about/privacy.

**Google AdSense**  
Google AdSense This website uses Google AdSense, a service for the integration of ads offered by Google Inc. ("Google"). The provider of this service is Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA. Google AdSense uses so-called "cookies"; i.e. text files that are stored on your computer and that make it possible to analyse your use of this website. Google AdSense also uses so-called Web Beacons (invisible graphics).

These Web Beacons can be used to analyse information, such as visitor traffic data, on this website. The information generated by the cookies and the Web Beacons concerning the use of this website (including your IP address) and the delivery of advertising formats are transferred to a Google server in the United States, where they are archived.

Google may share this information with Google contracting partners. Google shall, however, not merge your IP address with any other of your data stored by Google. 5 / 7 The storage of the AdSense cookies is based on Art. 6 Sect. 1 lit. f GDPR.

The website operator has a legitimate interest in the analysis of user patterns, in order to optimize the operator’s web offerings and advertising. You can prevent the installation of these cookies by making a pertinent adjustment to your browser software settings; however, we have to point out that in this case you may not be able to use all of the functions of this website to their fullest extent.

By using this website, you declare your consent to the processing of the data we collect about you by Google in the manner described above and agree to the aforementioned purpose of use.

**Google Web Fonts**  
For uniform representation of fonts, this page uses web fonts provided by Google. When you open a page, your browser loads the required web fonts into your browser cache to display texts and fonts correctly. For this purpose your browser has to establish a direct connection to Google servers. Google thus becomes aware that our web page was accessed via your IP address. The use of Google Web fonts is done in the interest of a uniform and attractive presentation of our website. This constitutes a justified interest pursuant to Art. 6 (1) (f) DSGVO.

If your browser does not support web fonts, a standard font is used by your computer. Further information about handling user data, can be found at https://developers.google.com/fonts/faq and in Google's privacy policy at https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/.
